("Lovefool" by The Cardigans)
♪ Dear I fear we're facing a problem ♪
♪ You love me no longer I know and ♪
♪ Maybe there is nothing that I can do ♪
♪ To make you do ♪
♪ Mama tells me I shouldn't bother ♪
♪ That I ought just stick to another man ♪
♪ A man that surely deserves me ♪
♪ But I think you do ♪
♪ So I cry and I pray and I beg ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Fool me fool me ♪
♪ Go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Pretend that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ So I cry and I beg for you to ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout anything but you ♪
♪ Lately I have desperately pondered ♪
♪ Spent my nights awake and I wonder ♪
♪ What I could have done in another way ♪
♪ To make you stay ♪
♪ Reason will not lead to solution ♪
♪ I will end up lost in confusion ♪
♪ I don't care if you really care ♪
♪ As long as you don't go ♪
♪ So I cry I pray and I beg ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Fool me fool me ♪
♪ Go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Pretend that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ So I cry and I beg for you to ♪
♪ Love me love me ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout anything but you ♪
♪ Love me love me say that you love me ♪
♪ Fool me fool me go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me love me I
know that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout anything but you ♪